{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"520aaacb-3b62-4300-82cb-1ff2e7cf1c8b"},"exam":{"id":"80665b75-76cb-4eec-a51e-84e039c249f1","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"10c453b6-5a2e-4615-9042-6c6fc00a7724","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authorization\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the Authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authorization is a part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":true}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"5rgnown1-vlu1-k6s2-9cwf-bvemaocz7dod","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the document used to grant permissions to users, groups, and roles?","explanation":"A Policy is the document used to grant permissions to users, groups, and roles.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/access_policies.html","title":"IAM Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"51359e8b51c63b87d50cb1bab73380e2","text":"Policy","correct":true},{"id":"888a77f5ac0748b6c8001822417df8b6","text":"Protocol","correct":false},{"id":"3e9adbb1694363232ef581246d090ea7","text":"Paradigm","correct":false},{"id":"88e23d388b9ab82cfa398a2fdb26467f","text":"Passbook","correct":false}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false}]},{"id":"fxef69cs-hn8k-lhl3-tlj6-g8e4sf2o4lud","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are programmatic access types enabling users to interact with AWS services?","explanation":"The CLI, the API, and the SDK are programmatic access types enabling users to interact with AWS services, as long as they are authorized to do so. PHP is a seperate programming language.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"Programmatic Access to AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"db974238714ca8de634a7ce1d083a14f","text":"API","correct":true},{"id":"f20e3c5e54c0ab3d375d660b3f896f6a","text":"SDK","correct":true},{"id":"91af5705f16502125e8b2187e64202c0","text":"CLI","correct":true},{"id":"2fec392304a5c23ac138da22847f9b7c","text":"PHP","correct":false}]},{"id":"3t2ov1u1-nwtz-6899-vmu9-eui5f3olrp6l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allow you to make entire buckets (like one hosting an S3 website) public?","explanation":"Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets, whereas Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/example-bucket-policies.html","title":"Bucket Policy Examples"}],"answers":[{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"5a804d2999d40df9fee58c79e96c4bc6","text":"Bucket Policies","correct":true},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false}]},{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false},{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true}]},{"id":"b386cdc3-9626-47e1-9be3-a4d78c363ad4","domain":"security","question":"Instead of relying on a single data center to provide its services across the world, AWS relies on several physical locations, each of which consists of one or more data centers. What are the official names for these physical locations and data centers?","explanation":"The physical locations from which AWS provides its services are known as Regions. Each Region consists of at least two Availability Zone, which can have anywhere from one data center to several of them.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/","title":"Global Infrastructures Regions and AZs"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb27078790943273979b82fd00f61dd1","text":" Sections; Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"c4bc6e143511ce56ce0ac41624e4c370","text":"Regions; Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2015015e824f6bbbc098e8b097d2dbda","text":"Regions; data centers","correct":false},{"id":"02da4e23b021b2dfa7ed963444ab3325","text":"Locations; data centers","correct":false}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"c127gqer-wn02-ljaa-xx5a-jpsogr3yw2ij","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services are free to use?","explanation":"Whilst all of these services are free to use, the things they create or interact with can incur charges. For instance, a CloudFormation template is free to run, but if it creates an EC2 instance, you will be paying for that EC2 instance. Whilst some of the other services do have free tier entitlements or features, as a service, they do have general costs associated with them","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/services/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"d85c80578ad0849a611c1056b63e385c","text":"VPC","correct":true},{"id":"caa58cad8d490fcdf1da0862623481fc","text":"Auto-Scaling","correct":true}]},{"id":"719cc66e-ayev-f5lb-zoet-xaar4i1a3kub","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following EC2 options is best for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns?","explanation":"Reserved instances are the most economical option for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns - in this consumption method, you commit to using resources for a period of time for a reduced cost. On-Demand is great for when you don't have predictable patterns as you only pay for when you are using the resources. Spot works when your workload is interruptible and doesn't need to be available all the time.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"}],"answers":[{"id":"ead2a4026c18cbaca9c93c0974c23f89","text":"Dedicated Host","correct":false},{"id":"bad26119751b8bdb0b46bff9a096f500","text":"On-Demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"82a1ac91-eb42-41c9-b216-39000de68a5c","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following statements are true about who can use IAM roles?","explanation":"A role can be used by either an IAM user in the same AWS account as the role or a user in a different AWS account. A role can also be used by a web service that AWS offers; a prime example is Amazon EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_terms-and-concepts.html","title":"IAM Role Terms and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"df8acd03a312147855a4dbb0fc3cad51","text":"A web service offered by providers other than AWS","correct":false},{"id":"31124384faad90d323f0ac8b670e3d5f","text":"An IAM user in the same AWS account as the role","correct":true},{"id":"bf2d86ed19745c25bb11a0239b17b7a5","text":"An IAM user in a different AWS account than the role","correct":true},{"id":"85f661e32207f8f663f531db040bc97a","text":"A web service offered by AWS","correct":true}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false}]},{"id":"7ed103d1-670b-487f-aa14-6d5e29084eb2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models automatically adjusts charges as your usage changes?","explanation":"Savings Plans is the only Amazon EC2 pricing model that provides the flexibility of adjusting charges depending on the amount of usage, thereby saving money in the process.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/savingsplans/","title":"Savings Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":false},{"id":"29068f6044e3fedf44165e646a2d2bb1","text":"Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":false},{"id":"b9912bfb6c79dc963ccc7e74d0ef9b36","text":"Savings Plan","correct":true}]},{"id":"9a62e30f-6366-4ba3-a6f9-29118a4432d8","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the Reserved Instance pricing model?","explanation":"Reserved instances are a great way of reducing costs on long running applications with predictable workloads. Even if the money is not available to make upfront payments, using Reserved Instances over longer periods can still be useful for cost savings","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"642a643c75d27712431a1b79c28e8cc5","text":"Unpredictable workloads","correct":false},{"id":"f5bfd0de9a22ee48b87ae246ed4f4042","text":"CAPEX vs OPEX charging model","correct":true},{"id":"e757909a259f51f248d287636899abda","text":"Ability to bid on the lowest compute price possible","correct":false},{"id":"79c233b246a21fbcf2c865dcef7f0791","text":"Predictable workload types","correct":true}]},{"id":"9pyttsq9-bl16-280g-vfrs-2qkodijvmrmg","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid ways for an IAM user to manage AWS resources?","explanation":"The two types of access are AWS Management Console access and Programmatic Access. Programmatic access is available via the AWS API, the CLI, and the SDKs - and an IAM user can use all these methods. Security Groups control network traffic to EC2 instances, and do not provide access to managing AWS Resources. Emergency Access is not a feature of IAM.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/UsingIAM.html","title":"Controlling Access to Amazon EC2 Resources"}],"answers":[{"id":"2fbca8dcca63ba9048e556de831897b1","text":"AWS Management Console access","correct":true},{"id":"8a49c0263f565565dafd85b396e5779a","text":"Security Group access via the AWS command line","correct":false},{"id":"2558c4af417f61e5475cc6e21268dd5b","text":"Emergency access via Identity Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"4d2e898f57bc396b4f79b35d5cc7a4c1","text":"Using the AWS Software Developers Kit","correct":true},{"id":"8f12104b24647e69720266d8744a70c1","text":"Programmatic access via the command line","correct":true}]},{"id":"e4e33d76-4ad4-48e6-8420-50d958d0c8a9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are part of the AWS storage services category?","explanation":"S3, EFS, and AWS Backup are three of AWS’s storage services. RDS and Redshift are classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":true},{"id":"35686630aa3baddc18c904374e570233","text":"Amazon RDS","correct":false},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"f7b96044a16becafecad63df1725e9c8","text":"Amazon EFS","correct":true},{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":true}]},{"id":"uqrnb9d8-haf3-bm5v-dcoo-t32fx6qgqhwi","domain":"tech","question":"Your application needs a MySQL database, but you need better performance than you could get running MySQL on EC2. Which of the following AWS services should you consider?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed MySQL database. It delivers up to 5X the performance of a MySQL database running on EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"f8d3b65d8479a31ebf67cb18dd0a4641","text":"Neptune","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"cykf25tw-ja73-62pe-bg44-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking AWS is responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, AWS is responsible for security OF the cloud - meaning that it is responsible for the infrastructure (hardware and software) which is used to deliver cloud services to customers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"17e0b507a41c19ff7684c3bf9d56497f","text":"None of security - security is up to the customer to manage","correct":false},{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true},{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"382b7116-1f69-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum number of IAM users you can add to an AWS account at the same time?","explanation":"You can add up to 10 users at one time at the IAM console.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_users_create.html","title":"Creating an IAM User in Your AWS Account"}],"answers":[{"id":"98f13708210194c475687be6106a3b84","text":"20","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":true},{"id":"e4da3b7fbbce2345d7772b0674a318d5","text":"5","correct":false}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef32cbf3-49b8-406a-aa2d-eaff05300839","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are separate from Regions and AZs. The number of Edge Locations around the world is greater than that of Regions and Availability Zones, in order to reduce latency between your content and your customers - the more that exist, the greater the chance there is one where you need it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5810cb8fea9cc8e7773f9cc96fdd6c51","text":"There are more Regions than Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"78f3c24434277d629cc0a0d14f18c598","text":"There are more Edge locations than Availability zones","correct":true},{"id":"9fe244cde3895fdb2a60650e6154c15b","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"b8ecf41dfa2a8f2d576a9407c87dadf5","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false},{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true}]},{"id":"a0b65082-209c-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"By default, how many buckets per AWS Account can you create with the Amazon S3 service?","explanation":"By default, you can create up to 100 S3 buckets per AWS account. However, you can request for additional buckets by submitting a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd","text":"100","correct":true},{"id":"8e296a067a37563370ded05f5a3bf3ec","text":"25","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":false},{"id":"cee631121c2ec9232f3a2f028ad5c89b","text":"500","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"fde3bfdf-a9fa-4476-b785-b8de7b315aeb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following languages can be used to author CloudFormation templates?","explanation":"CloudFormation supports both JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) and YAML Ain't Markup Language (aka YAML) for authoring CloudFormation templates.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/working-with-templates-cfn-designer-json-editor.html","title":"Integrated JSON and YAML Editor"}],"answers":[{"id":"9463f87bbed1fcdacfb8d40e185ca2bc","text":"YAML","correct":true},{"id":"a7f5f35426b927411fc9231b56382173","text":"Python","correct":false},{"id":"2a52ba6e26e550c59e15affa051e478b","text":"CAMEL","correct":false},{"id":"0ecd11c1d7a287401d148a23bbd7a2f8","text":"JSON","correct":true}]},{"id":"43e53065-cb82-4d76-a75d-8407d8f0d339","domain":"tech","question":"What two things make up a tag?","explanation":"Each tag consists of a key and a value. For each resource, each tag key must be unique, and each tag key can have only one value.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"22c56699c70b96c6c2351fbf86177472","text":"Primary key value","correct":false},{"id":"897356954c2cd3d41b221e3f24f99bba","text":"Key","correct":true},{"id":"689202409e48743b914713f96d93947c","text":"Value","correct":true},{"id":"b5e6800855208fbd66985d5f570ffd70","text":"Encryption String","correct":false}]},{"id":"xun4oj55-ptum-ekl7-y5ot-pqhc5t5psvxi","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following support plans features unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases?","explanation":"Both Enterprise and Business support plans feature unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false},{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true},{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false}]},{"id":"768b0aa8-1fea-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon S3 Standard storage will you get for no cost?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 5 GB of standard S3 storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"b3dd42c7956751be5d38b5c0cb2e09c0","text":"5 TB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":true},{"id":"0d642755e7f12f7563e3db33bd0c39cb","text":"1 GB","correct":false},{"id":"3a6d03856b824be771cdd922375d59db","text":"20 GB","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a9b87ae-3552-46ad-9cee-605c6dc2d534","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services can be used to create billing alarms?","explanation":"The CloudWatch service is used to create billing alarms. The Cost Explorer service is used to creates custom reports that facilitate the understanding of the organization's costs and data usage. Macie is a service used to identify sensitive data such as personally identifiable information (PII) stored in S3. The Athena service analyzes data using SQL queries stored in S3.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","title":"Creating a Billing Alarm to Monitor Your Estimated AWS Charges"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true},{"id":"582ca45acfd3e21caca8b786c1413850","text":"Athena","correct":false},{"id":"689485d385032d81c9cc43cbc981549a","text":"Macie","correct":false},{"id":"619ed6d20397878e9706fe9fa7c44579","text":"Cost Explorer","correct":false}]},{"id":"gz05o0zm-686t-arfr-tr1s-7wjbwyv832dv","domain":"tech","question":"You need to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Which of the following must be present to enable this access?","explanation":"A NAT Gateway is required to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, but don't actually process or transmit traffic. Security Groups and Network Access Control Lists are used to protect resources from traffic, and by themselves do not enable access to the internet - although they need to be properly configured to let traffic bound for the internet out.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/vpc-nat-gateway.html","title":"About NAT Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8ca0f1328403ec0d05ed995272d74715","text":"NAT Gateway","correct":true}]},{"id":"i24lu8u9-bdxm-hnxr-9xkq-ogorvl1cou1f","domain":"tech","question":"In which of the following is CloudFront content cached?","explanation":"Edge Locations consist of over 200+ points of presence around the world which provide fast entry into Amazon's global network. Because of how widespread they are, users can connect to their nearest Edge Location, and have their traffic sent through Amazon's fast Global Network to reach the resources it needs sooner. This is how CloudFront's caching mechanism works. There are far less Availability Zones and Regions than Edge Locations, which is why CloudFront does not use them for caching content.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"e95464b98c902ebad35546ca12a620a4","text":"Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"f447ac856e7e72435904956e3b15f433","text":"Region","correct":false},{"id":"47df2b78ac4b3edfbf1c6d0b2a64c579","text":"Data Center","correct":false},{"id":"ec50121a3fdd0fb561e14291a5741b6e","text":"Edge Location","correct":true}]},{"id":"11cddf60-2bb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain any infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https: //aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false}]},{"id":"1wf5g4cl-1eei-cxmu-red3-wkm59ywgq86h","domain":"tech","question":"With AWS Relational Database Service (RDS), which of the following are you responsible for?","explanation":"You are responsible only for the optimization of your application that uses RDS - AWS will take care of the rest as this is considered a Managed Service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"bc967dc2d57e6eff184a821bf7577a80","text":"Scaling","correct":false},{"id":"7b4eef372e52b848a7e0f93e59b06d70","text":"All of these","correct":false},{"id":"5f4dc8e976d91d69670d0a272e0ee6e3","text":"Database software installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"6bb1aca01fa54044f3ec9ae581b4620f","text":"Operating system installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"a514531b35c90598677ddee7c4b1afd9","text":"The optimization of your application using RDS","correct":true},{"id":"89f8bb80ca1403422295c6ad48f8cac7","text":"Database backups","correct":false}]},{"id":"a31cc98c-2146-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following scenarios demand the use of an egress-only Internet gateway?","explanation":"An egress-only Internet gateway is used for IPv6 addresses only. It allows outbound communication from instances in your VPC to the Internet, and prevents the Internet from initiating connection with the instances.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/egress-only-internet-gateway.html","title":"Egress-Only Internet Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"01fc59aa00d3c5c5c0ffff43b05a22a0","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv4","correct":false},{"id":"5be0953999314fd060740ef201866d64","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv6","correct":true},{"id":"350b0f16434bcd3e211471390f1d840b","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv6","correct":false},{"id":"9e839253188e9d5f95d2e2278c3bad32","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv4","correct":false}]},{"id":"g817t8h6-2yd3-mhf7-wf2v-n82br09qszt7","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance certifications attests to the security of the AWS platform regarding credit card transactions?","explanation":"PCI DSS is a compliance program which must be followed by any organizations handling Credit Card data. AWS has achieved a PCI Level 1 certification, the highest level available","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"faf72a9a0f8e7e240ee1346d6e2056e3","text":"SOC 1","correct":false},{"id":"7829c763646fba446ea5831ef095f756","text":"ISO 27001","correct":false},{"id":"7aa6bd3f5ca63135c1f75edd80d7a6ba","text":"SOC 2","correct":false},{"id":"74073bf9c7bfe155fe513fd4624ae2f2","text":"PCI DSS Level 1","correct":true}]},{"id":"p591e7kl-wfkp-78wh-zz8y-kf2mmf34gdw1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are steps you should take in securing your AWS account?","explanation":"The Root account should have MFA enabled, due to it's unlimited access to an account. You should always create IAM users for individual users, since the Root account should never be used for actual work. Groups should be used to delegate permissions to the users you create, instead of individual assigning policies to IAM users since it makes administration easier. Assigning policies directly to any user is not a good idea, since it can be hard to figure out who has access to what resources with many users.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM best practice"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_create_for-user.html","title":"IAM using Roles"}],"answers":[{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"8ef2b84b0ea8ddc5ae686a44387d63d7","text":"Activate Multi-factor Authentication (MFA) on your root account.","correct":true},{"id":"2e679971f295b42ffb5f0228883437fb","text":"Use groups to delegate access to IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"bd3cf659e9d378f1808cdb33b54baa84","text":"Assign policies directly to your administrative users","correct":false}]},{"id":"3617c0aa-2fa9-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"For enhanced technical support, some AWS Support plans enable you to have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases. Which of the following choices offer this feature?","explanation":"With either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you can provide have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"2srflb2w-gpba-wyok-a3ts-v64r4v1vd57h","domain":"tech","question":"You use containers to host your microservices, and you need to route traffic to those applications using a single load balancer. Which of the following services should you use to accomplish this?","explanation":"This routing can be done only with an Application Load Balancer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/details/#details","title":"About the ALB"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"7be6a0f173a965818e92c1df46c6626e","text":"AWS CodeDeploy","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":true}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false}]},{"id":"48f2d351-b6b2-4615-a662-be8ca8a2b84f","domain":"tech","question":"Trusted Advisor is classified as what type of AWS service?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is a Management and Governance tool. It guides you on how to best manage your resources based on AWS best practices in five categories.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"c784a652acefe771f7a2853db61a07ae","text":"Application Integration","correct":false},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"458f5f8faf1e6121d97d167d4f94db24","text":"Management & Governance","correct":true},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false},{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false},{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true}]},{"id":"j55neiwz-9leq-mmdm-z3qb-rjp9ll7te3ey","domain":"tech","question":"By default, what can a Private Subnet communicate with?","explanation":"By default, a Private Subnet can only communicate with other subnets in the same VPC, be they Private or Public. In order to communicate to the internet, a NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway are required, and to enable communication between subnets in different VPCs the VPCs must first be peered.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html#vpc-subnet-basics","title":"VPC and Subnet Basics"}],"answers":[{"id":"2833f376428e487505135ddd3e3dfa83","text":"Other Private Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true},{"id":"bc073365b9c1fbd0626a854e3b600009","text":"The internet","correct":false},{"id":"6aff3455ef4ee9f91852d846278af179","text":"Private Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false},{"id":"8d6c6a7fbfb26a46f1cb21637cb6efc6","text":"Public Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true},{"id":"fc10601fc9c6d89cc325196b308a5d09","text":"Public Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false},{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customers’ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true},{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false}]},{"id":"27cc5e9d-2482-4135-8a9f-9cf65f6e1688","domain":"tech","question":"What does WAF stand for?","explanation":"WAF stands for Web Application Firewall, so named because it monitors web application requests and allows or prevents traffic based on a defined ruleset and known vulnerabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/waf-chapter.html","title":"AWS WAF"}],"answers":[{"id":"f822badbd1112c49db5910159248fc40","text":"Web Application Firehose","correct":false},{"id":"8b3d064fc45bbaa3b52eeb560d6c03d3","text":"Web Analytics File","correct":false},{"id":"34ee1981f6dccd1866d4b35375201161","text":"Web Application Firewall","correct":true},{"id":"4baadf1798a3bbde4f338736486c76fb","text":"Web Application Forecast","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"riqpy09p-2mos-4v71-m59a-je7iknttb5c4","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following is generally not billed for on the AWS platform?","explanation":"Data Transferred in to AWS is almost always free of charge (excluding large transfer services, like AWS Snowball). The reason for this, and best way to remember it is that AWS don't mind you transferring lots of data in to their services, since you'll already be paying to use and store it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"72a2694d2bcec74cfbc3e76e2e8d6c24","text":"Data-in","correct":true},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"a5227beaedc6d59181cd9199f25d32ce","text":"Data-out","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false}]},{"id":"aabc59b3-b883-454e-8336-dac6f49eb7c3","domain":"security","question":"You are a Systems Administrator who has just started adding IAM users to your company’s AWS account. However, you worry that the users will not create passwords strong enough to prevent unauthorized access. What is the most reliable way to ensure that users are using strong passwords?","explanation":"Use Identity and Access Management (IAM) to apply an IAM password policy. While awareness and training are critical to developing good security practices, the most reliable option is to use an IAM Password Policy, which won't allow users to use lower strength passwords.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"da197ad4fa2d98027feab02afd84d7fc","text":"Speak with each IAM user individually about the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"6cb5679faafdf0c247c2543bdca0e635","text":"Apply an IAM password policy to ensure users create appropriately strong passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"a08ccc3650b327c02cd13367d8ffa875","text":"Hold an AWS webinar to stress the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"2ef38712519600d72d012e44a6dcb5a3","text":"Ask for the password of each user and create a much stronger one by yourself.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"110c4336-0571-488d-bc05-fc2fd78887b4","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the name of AWS Regions designed to allow U.S. government agencies and customers to move significantly sensitive workloads into the cloud?","explanation":"AWS GovCloud is an AWS Region specially designed to host sensitive data and regulated workloads from U.S. government agencies and customers. In addition, it addresses the most stringent U.S. government security and compliance requirements. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/govcloud-us/","title":"AWS GovCloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"ce8b567fad0737a23a7c47b5d781acae","text":"AWS GovRegion","correct":false},{"id":"528af0ceafec0ca0b002f96151614f38","text":"AWS Government Region","correct":false},{"id":"55e430ef34ef9e18d752b0c39ae96c4a","text":"AWS Government Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"6f76628274759630f18deb508898fa64","text":"AWS GovCloud","correct":true}]}]}}}}
